There are a lot of faces.
顔多いね
We had sex, a lot.
エッチしたね、いっぱい
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Let's try again.
もう一回しようよ
Besides, let's take it off.
その上、脱いでみようか
I'm standing on a chair.
椅子立ちになっとるわ
Awesome, I'll try that.
すごい、そうやってみる
It's crossed.
クロスしてるね
It's okay to take it back.
裏取っちゃっていいよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
You have an erotic face
エロい顔してる
hey.
ね
Are you going to sleep downstairs too?
下 も寝ちゃうか
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Could you open your legs a little?
足ちょっと開いてごらん?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Why don't you open it yourself?
自分で開いてごらん?
That's good.
よろしいね
So why don't you try opening it again yourself?
じゃあもう一回自分で開いてごらん?
Stay strong.
しっかりしてて
It comes with something like a tissue.
ティッシュみたいなのがついてる
Could you please open it again?
もう 一 回 開いてごらん?
It's so erotic.
すごいエロいし
Can you take your pants back?
パンツ、出返してごらん?
I can't stand it.
我慢できないよ
It's slimy.
ぬるぬるだね
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
copper?
どう?
It's really tight.
すっごいきつい
copper?
どう?
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
It's terrible, it's terrible, it's terrible.
や ばい、やばい、やばい
Yeah?
うん?
Poop?
うんち?
amazing.
すごい
This is terrible, this is terrible.
やばい、やばい、これ